Guide to the Architects' brochures, 1975-2002.
Architects' brochures
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Architects' brochures, 1975-2002.
8051
.4 cubic feet.
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Brochures from architectural firms showcasing their work.
Originally sent as recruiting tools to the College of Architecture, Art, and Planning.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Brochures from architectural firms showcasing their work. Firms include Amenta/Emma, Bowie Gridley Architects, Burt Hill Kosar Rittelmann Associates, The Design Alliance, EYP Mission Critical Facilities, Inc., Hellmuth, Obata + Kassabaum, Hillier Architecture, HOLT Architects, Mancini Duffy, McCall Design Group, Michael Graves Architects, Odell, Perkins Eastman Architects, Simon Martin Vegue Winkelstein Moris.
Also, "A Proposal for a branch bank of The City National Bank and Trust Company, Gloversville, New York," Edgar Tafel Architect, n.d.; "Schematic Presentation for Atlantic City Performing Arts Center," Taliesin Associated Architects of the Frank Lloyd Wright Foundation, William Wesley Peters, Architect, 1975.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Amenta/Emma Architects.; Bowie Gridley Architects.; Burt Hill Kosar Rittelmann Associates.; Design Alliance.; EYP Mission Critical Facilities, Inc.; Hellmuth, Obata & Kassabaum.; Hillier Architecture.; HOLT Architects.; Mancini Duffy.; McCall Design Group.; Michael Graves Architects.; Odell Associates Inc.; Perkins Eastman Architects.; Simon Martin Vegue Winkelstein Moris
Subjects:
Architects--20th century.; Architectural firms--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Amenta/Emma Architects 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bowie/Gridley Architects [2002] (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Burt Hill Kosar Rittelmann Associates undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Design Alliance Architects [2002] (Box 1, Folder 4)
- EYP Mission Critical Facilities [2002] (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Hellmuth, Obata & Kassabaum / New York City undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Hillier Architecture 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Hoffman O'Brien Look Taube & Chiang, P. C. Architects, Planners, and Interior Designers (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Mancini-Duffy / Architecture, Planning, Interior Design 1999+ (Box 1, Folder 9)
- McCall Design Group 2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Michael Graves Architects [2001] (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Odell Planning, Architecture, Engineering, Interior Design, Landscape Architecture 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Perkins Eastman Architects [1991+] (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Simon, Martin-Vegue, Winkelstein, Moris / Architecture, Interior Design, Planning 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Proposal for a branch bank of The City National Bank and Trust Company, Gloversville, New York and Schematic Presentation for Atlantic City Performing Arts Center 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)